{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "question": "Write 13 in German",
      "answer": "dreizehn"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 16 in German",
      "answer": "sechzehn"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 19 in German",
      "answer": "neunzehn"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 21 in German",
      "answer": "einundzwanzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 24 in German",
      "answer": "vierundzwanzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 28 in German",
      "answer": "achtundzwanzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 30 in German",
      "answer": "dreißig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 40 in German",
      "answer": "vierzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 70 in German",
      "answer": "siebzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 100 in German",
      "answer": "einhundert"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 114 in German",
      "answer": "einhundertvierzehn"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 132 in German",
      "answer": "einhundertzweiunddreißig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 1000 in German",
      "answer": "eintausend"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 1256 in German",
      "answer": "eintausendzweihundertsechsundfünfzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 1987 in German",
      "answer": "eintausendneunhundertsiebenundachtzig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Write 2024 in German",
      "answer": "zweitausendvierundzwanzig"
    }
  ]
}
